After 10 years in prison,
when I was wronged to kill my father
and lose my mother,
I should find out
Brother Ping An.
Hey, Brother Ping An,
if you make a fortune when you
go out in the future,
don't forget your little brother,
Go slowly,
brother
Brother
I'm old,
I'm already 31,
and I'm still a boy.
Okay,
no more ink marks,
go home
Okay,
it's fine.
Daughter-in-law,
I picked up my brother
and came back.
I'll be back soon.
Well,
what's the matter?
I have to ask a section of the tiger
to be there.
If you are thirsty,
don't take it to your heart.
Your sister-in-law is like this.
People have knives and
tofu hearts.
It's okay, brother,
The village chief is dressed.
Hahaha,
give money,
people in Randao
War.
Hey haha,
boy,
you still recognize some,
three tips,
hahaha.
Master,
your tips are here,
Sister-in-law let me play.
Chant.